freeclassifieds.com 2019-03-20

# Free Classifieds - Buy or Sell anything for free, freeclassifieds.com!

**PRIVACY POLICY**

This policy is intended to help you understand how freeclassifieds.com, its subsidiaries and affiliates (“freeclassifieds.com,” we,” or “us”) collect, use and safeguard the information you provide on our websites. 

**What we collect**

We aggregate both anonymous and personal data. What we collect depends on what you do when you use our websites and on what personal information you elect to give us.

**Anonymous data**

We collect anonymous data when you visit our websites, including your internet address, the time of your visit and the pages that you view. We use this information to monitor and improve the performance of our websites so that we can continue to effectively and reliably provide useful services for our visitors and our company.

**Personal information**

If you wish, you can provide us with personal information about yourself by using the contact forms and email addresses on this site. This information includes your name, business name, mailing address, email address and phone number. We only collect this information directly from you and only when you elect to provide it. If you accept the opportunity to be contacted by us, either by personal email, telephone, mail or email newsletter, you can revoke that acceptance at any time by contacting us at the contact points specified below.

Depending upon which of our services you are utilizing, the types of non-public personal information that we may collect include:

·   Name, postal address, email address, and telephone number, birth date, shipping address and credit card information;

·   Information we receive from you on applications, forms and in other communications to us, whether in writing, in person, by telephone or by any other means;

·   Information about your transactions with us or others; 

·   Information from your transactions with us; 

·   Information we receive from your computer when you visit our website that is unique to e-commerce transactions. It may include the website you visited before ours, your operating system and statistical information on Web traffic and usage patterns; and

·   Information we receive from you pertaining to content, remarks, suggestions, ideas, graphics, reviews or comments, advertisements or listings for products and/or services, or other information communicated to freeclassifieds.com through this website (“Submissions”) that you have experienced.

Personal information we gather through our online forms or information that you otherwise provide to us for purposes of conducting business may be released to our business partners. We may sell client personal information, and may provide client personal information to persons or organizations outside freeclassifieds.com that are doing business on freeclassifieds.com’s behalf for their own marketing purposes. Any personal or anonymous data may be used by freeclassifieds.com for any purpose.

**Profile**

We may store information that we collect through cookies, log files, and/or clear gifs to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the user’s personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user’s visit to our websites, and to direct pertinent information to them. Your profile with other third parties. 

**What we share**

freeclassifieds.com may share aggregate and personally identifiable information pertaining to your profile and Submissions that you have provided to us. Information pertaining to the Submissions may be sold, leased, or otherwise provided to our business partners. 

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on freeclassifieds.com or its websites; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of freeclassifieds.com; or (c) act to protect the personal safety of the employees of freeclassifieds.com and other users of the websites.

**Use of Personal Data**

Personal information provided by users may be used for marketing and informational purposes by freeclassifieds.com, its subsidiaries and affiliates, and its business partners. freeclassifieds.com may rent, sell or otherwise distribute to its business partners, your personal information entered on this site. While we use all reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your information, freeclassifieds.com will have no liability for disclosure of any information obtained due to errors in transmission or the unauthorized acts of third parties. 

**Children's Privacy**

We believe that protecting the privacy of children is very important. Our websites are not designed to attract individuals under the age of 13. Use of our websites is restricted to those over the age of 13. In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we do not collect or store any personal information, even in aggregate, about children under the age of 13. If we discover we have received any information from a child under the age of 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe that freeclassifieds.com has any information from or about anyone under the age of 13, please contact us at the contact points specified below.

**California Residents**

As of January 1, 2005, California law permits users that reside in California to request certain information regarding the disclosure of personal information collected by freeclassifieds.com to third parties for marketing purposes. 

**Linked Sites**

Our websites may contain links to various other websites. freeclassifieds.com assumes no responsibility for the content or practices of websites linked through our websites and such linking should not suggest or imply any affiliation or endorsement by freeclassifieds.com of the linked website. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by our websites. 

**Choice/Opt-out**

Our users are given the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having their information used for marketing and information communications. Users can change or opt-out on how they are contacted at any time by writing to the contact points specified below.

**Business Transitions**

If freeclassifieds.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition, or sales of a portion of its assets, your personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. You will be notified via prominent notice on our website for 30 days prior to a change of ownership or control of your personal information. If, as a result of the business transition, your personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, you will be given choice consistent with the one outlined in “Revisions to this Policy” (below).

**Security**

We follow industry standards and practices to safeguard all of the information, anonymous and personal, that we collect. If users have any questions about the security at our websites, users can contact us at the contact points specified below.

**Revisions to this Policy**

freeclassifieds.com reserves the right to periodically revise this policy. Please check this page periodically for changes. The document revision date displayed below will indicate when this policy was last revised. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

If we are planning to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not you allow us to continue to use and maintain your information under our new policy. Of course, if you have opted out of all communication with us or deleted/deactivated your account, you will not be contacted and your personal information will not be used or maintained under the new policy. 

**Contact Information:**

Questions about this privacy policy should be directed to : 

legal@freeclassifieds.com

Please use this contact information only for privacy policy matters. For all other inquiries, refer to the Contact Us section of our home page.

This document was last revised on 11/05/2010.
